<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Video - Tag - Yike Li</title>
        <link>https://yike-l.github.io/tags/video/</link>
        <description>Video - Tag - Yike Li</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 17:48:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yike-l.github.io/tags/video/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>A VR-Oriented Efficient 3D Scene Synthesis System</title>
    <link>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/vr-orientedsystem/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 17:48:48 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Yike Li</author>
    <guid>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/vr-orientedsystem/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/VR-OrientedSystem.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Abstract With the rapid development of virtual reality (VR), the demand for 3D scenes has been boosted dramatically. Massive algorithms of automatic arrangement for objects have been proposed to solve this problem. However, few of these techniques are applied in VR. To make the automatic 3D scene synthesizing more suitable for VR, we put forward a series of innovative methods, considering the interaction and presentation features in VR. Our methods, including automatic scene synthesis and intelligent scene editing, contribute to the efï¬ciency and effectiveness of VR scene synthesis.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Natural Hand Remapping: Velocity Adaptive Hand Manipulation for VR</title>
    <link>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/handremapping/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 17:47:24 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Yike Li</author>
    <guid>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/handremapping/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/HandRemapping.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Automatic Generation of Commercial Scenes</title>
    <link>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/commercialscenes/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 17:46:52 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Shao-Kui Zhang, Jia-Hong Liu, **Yike Li**, Tianyi Xiong, Ke-Xin Ren, Hongbo Fu, Song-Hai Zhang</author>
    <guid>https://yike-l.github.io/posts/commercialscenes/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/CommercialScenes.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Abstract Commercial scenes such as markets and shops are everyday scenes for both virtual scenes and real-world interior designs. However, existing literature on interior scene synthesis mainly focuses on formulating and optimizing residential scenes such as bedrooms, living rooms, etc. Existing literature typically presents a set of relations among objects. It recognizes each furniture object as the smallest unit while optimizing a residential room. However, object relations become less critical in commercial scenes since shelves are often placed next to each other so that pre-calculated relations of objects are less needed.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
